shuttledirect.com 2006-10-27

# Shuttle Direct: help

Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how Viajes Alameda collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our Web site.

The following are all parts of the Statement:

### Information Collection

When you browse Viajes Alameda's web site and have not registered for any online service from Viajes Alameda, you browse anonymously. Personal information -- such as your name, address, phone number or E-mail address -- is not collected as you browse. Viajes Alameda does, however, use cookies to collect information about how our site is used. Information, such as the server your computer is logged on to, your browser type (for example, Netscape or Internet Explorer), and whether you responded to a Viajes Alameda banner ad or E-mail is collected and tracked in aggregate. This information is used for the purpose of measuring response rates to banner ads and E-mail offers. If you would like to learn more about cookies, please read About Cookies for more information.

### Registration for Online Products and Services

In order to provide you with a particular product or service online, we may request that you supply us voluntarily with personal information, including your E-mail address and credit card number, for purposes such as correspondence, site registration, making a purchase, participating in online surveys and enabling us to provide an online product or service to you in an efficient manner, including developing or making offers of products and services in which you may be interested.

### Personalisation

If you are known to us as a registered user of an Viajes Alameda online service, we may combine information about your use of Viajes Alameda web site's with certain other online and offline information we have about you as a Viajes Alameda customer. We also use a cookie to enable our server to recognize you as a registered Viajes Alameda online service user when you re-enter our site.

### Information Use

We may use information you have given us, for example, to provide a service, ensure proper billing, measure consumer interest in our various services and inform you about products and services. If you provide us with your E-mail address or have done so in the past, or if we obtain your E-mail address from another source, we may send you E-mail offers. These offers may be based on information you provided in your initial transaction with us, in surveys, from information that may indicate purchasing preferences and lifestyle, as well as information available from external sources, such as merchants and marketing organisations. These E-mail offers come directly from Viajes Alameda.

When we send E-mails to you, we may be able to identify information about your E-mail address, such as whether you can read graphic-rich html E-mails. If your E-mail address is html-enabled, we may choose to send you graphic-rich html E-mails.

Please note that we do not provide your E-mail address to our business partners. However, we may send you offers on behalf of our business partners. Keep in mind that if you take advantage of an offer from an Viajes Alameda business partner and become their customer, they may independently wish to send offers to you. In this case, you will need to inform them separately if you wish to decline receiving future offers from them.

For an example of the types of special offers we may provide on behalf of our business partners to Viajes Alameda Cardmembers, please view the Blue Zone.

Our goal is to deliver offers to people who we believe will find them relevant and of value. Offers are developed and managed under strict conditions designed to safeguard the security and privacy of customer personal information. However, at any time you may request not to receive these offers.

### Declining E-mail Offers

Viajes Alameda provides customers with an easy means to decline receiving E-mail offers. Although some customers tell us they appreciate receiving notice of these carefully designed opportunities, we recognise the importance of providing you with choices. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers from us by simply replying to the E-mail and informing us of your preferences. All E-mail offers that you receive from Viajes Alameda will inform you of how to decline receiving further E-mail offers. Additionally, you may set or change your E-mail preferences online at any time.

### Children

We do not use Viajes Alameda web site's to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 18.

### Your Right of Access and Correction

If you ask us, we will tell you what information we hold about you and provide it to you in accordance with applicable law. There may be a charge for this as permitted by law. If you believe that any information we hold about you is incorrect or incomplete, you should write without delay to Viajes Alameda, Vía Emilio Ortuño, 15, E03501 Benidorm, Alicante, Spain. Any information which is found to be incorrect or incomplete will be corrected promptly.

### Linked Internet Sites

You should be aware that other Internet sites to which you link from Viajes Alameda web site's may contain privacy provisions that differ from the provisions provided herein.

### Changes to the Customer Internet Privacy Statement

Changes to our Internet Privacy Statement will be noted here so that you can be fully informed about the privacy protection we provide and your choices with regard to our use of personal information for marketing purposes. Date Last Revised: 01 April 2003
